So, hey guys welcome to our next video, so this is the final video for initial access
via Progen.
So, this is the one I was using, so this is one of the crack file, you know about the
crack file, it's a fake, not a fake, pirated license to software, so if any, if the software
cost will be like, more than 2,000, 3,000 I.S. I.N.R, there's a lot of software it will
be available for paid software, but you will be getting the software from the pilot
at websites like tar or any torrents or telegram, even in telegram or twitter, so this
kind of links you can download that software.
You will be downloading the Microsoft Windows M365 or Office 365 from in a crack version,
so everyone know about this, okay, so I will show this one of the software I have downloaded
from the telegram, this one of the screen decoder, let me will see how the detectors will
install the Progen were malicious code in here, okay, I need a few tools, I will download
the tools before, so let me go for to download few tools, so give me some time, yep, I need
a few tools, I already said, so the first tool will be, for knowing permission, like
the weird thing, so the two line process, Prokma, so this is the one of the tools which
I need, I will be downloading, first one, Prokma, and next tool which I need that will
be the TCP explorer, yeah TCP view and download this, so other tool, you can go for a process
hacker, so these are the tools that I need, first, so I was downloading this tool because
you need to understand how the Progen will work, and if you installed the crack versions
in your missions what will happen, and okay, so why the companies are saying to download
it from the legit bit website, okay, we will install all the tools first, let me install
the process hacker, I will be extracting this TCP view, okay, and we need to extract the
process monitor, we install the process hacker, these three tools, you can use other tools
as well, like YSR, like that, but this solution of money, to showcase how the Progen
version works, so now we got all the tools, so let's extract the crack to crack file,
so it's of 150, so here you can see I top screen recorder, this is the name which I have
taken from a telegram, so instead you can see there is a launcher version 1.1.12, so this
is my own experience, so I was searching for free tools, screen recording tools, in lot
of star websites and lot of websites, finally I got this, but when I tried to before installing
in my primary machine, so I tried installing in my VM machine, okay, to know about whether
this cracked file contain any virus or not, okay, so when I start installing this, I got
a very, very shocking scenarios, so let me show you, let me open the walk-on, before
installing that, because we need to understand, so what are the processes it is going to
communicate, we will go to the TCP view, also we need to understand what about the network
related activities and all, whether there is any connection has been going on or anything
we can download, we can open both of the tools, so now the prop monitors was monitoring
the process and the TCP view, here you can see all the network communications from your
machine, so now every tool has been ready, so let's install the launcher, it will still
running, let's see, so whether there is any, so it's showing operation did not come
to it successfully, because the file contain virus or potentiary unwanted softwares, so
maybe it installed and there is some malicious things there, there, so I will do one thing,
I will stop all the programs like defender programs, Windows defenders, so you can see
there is a scalloped flash here that has been recorded, I will do a lot on this device,
I will go to the, so the Windows defenders saying it might contain some viruses, but what
I will, I will be turning off all the protections before installing, because you know the
cracked files most of the, if you read the read me files in the cracked files, which you
are downloading, they will be saying turn off your antivirus softwares and then start
installation, so let me turn off the firewall as well, so we will, we will try installing
the things now, we will try running now, so now you can see the launch version one point
on has been opening, they will do s, so we will monitor, so what is happening inside the network,
if there is any suspicious traffic here, so this is some kind of a behavior analysis in
manner, so you can analyze what the x you will be doing, let us see, if you have used
the Prokma, let me search the process there it is, let me check for a process tree first,
here you can see launch or something has been installed, let me copy this, so after the
launch installation, so you can see the Java.exe and there is a, the Java, I didn't
install any Java program in my machine, okay, the first of all the next CMD has been opened
and here you can see something has been executed through the CMD, so it is a current
version, current field and something has been executed and you get Cp, so here you can find
it, did a lot of things in my machine, so see, we already covered the WMIC, it get some
information about the CPU and all and, so again there is some, it is getting some CPU
information, so I will do one thing, I will go to the launcher.exe and let me filter it
with the process activity of launcher, go to the filter option and filter it with the
process name, process name, you can give contains, you can paste the launcher 1.7 point
12 here, because this is the file which gets executed, you can add the item, let's see
it, get filter it out, so now you can find what the launcher did completely in our
machine, so you can find each and everything, you can find everything to see what actually
happened in the machine, so this is the way which I will be doing the malware analysis
sometime, it did a lot of things probably in our machine, so better what I will do, I will
save this file, we will save it as a CAC format and we will investigate that what happened
actually, what by one, let it get transferred, so we will do one thing, we will filter it
with the create file option, so we can see what the files has been created first, instead
you are measuring the extra files, the operation create file, then we can understand what
all the extra files the Trojan has been created, so these are some dear ones, so you need
some patience, so I will investigate this kind of file, so you can see it created some of the
term file from into this directory, so it did some Java related activities, so if you go
to that path, let me go to that, but I didn't installed any Java in machine, first of
all, let me go to that path in machine and we will see whether this directory contain
some malware, some Java related application, so it has been created, let's post that, so
all the Java related activities, so it has some other files, a EL of is something it created
some of the file, let's put some time, I just saved that, I don't, let's see our
log files are saved, instead of the machine or not, this is a log file, let me take the
CSE into my, into my primary machine, okay, so we will investigate from here
here, it will be better to investigate, we can filter everything here to filter that, we
will go for what other, so it will give each and every information, okay, everything will
be there, we will filter it by one by one, process create, filter the process create, so you
can see there is a, one process has been created Java, something.exe, and let's filter
the create file, create file, let me see what other files has been created, so here is
some CF install, these are the files, which has been created, so you can see launch.exe
under the update or bin or directory, we will go to the VM machines and we will see whether
the folder has been, some turns in the machine, let's focus on here, let's keep that, okay,
so here is the directory, so you need some patience to investigate and everything, that's
only thing here, the update or bin launch.ac, okay, let's go to C, C, users, user,
okay, this is about update or bin launch, maybe the folder will be fit and let me, so let
me do so all the hidden folders, yeah, now you can see the update, local, okay, it's not
a local term, like user update or bin, user, I have data, okay, okay, I think the folder
is not there, yeah, maybe it has been removed, we will check for other files, there's
a lot of things just in order, and you can see a lot of filters, you can see from here
here, and we will filter the right file and you will see what other files it has been
in, so the same it has opened a lot of Java later file from the machine, okay, okay,
so we will see what other images has been loaded, so these are the data that has been loaded
inside the host, let's see the red set value, so it returns some data here, this is the binary
data and that create, so some of the thread has been created, so this is a thread ID, so
these are activities, basically the launcher.exe has been did, let me do one thing, let
me, we will, we will solve this filter, operation, we will see any suspicious communication,
so in a previous time when I tested, there will be a lot of things has been loaded,
I was checking that, because there is an auto ID and there is a loaded.exe has been
installed and a lot more, but not actually seeing the hack, but if you see the created
file activities, the launcher, someone.exe did a lot of a species thing, okay.
>> [BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Yeah, this is a detailed version.
So, by this you can filter it, if before installing the practical information.
You just install the crack fed in your own virtual machine and you can check what will happen.
Once you execute this kind of a frozen was insert the machine, okay.
So, we will hop off this video and we will continue our discussion in the next video.
you guys, bye-bye.